peoplespharmacy.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy | The People's Pharmacy

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the PeoplesPharmacy.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information  
(etc.) 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. Or, if you want to send an article to a friend, you will need to submit the friend’s email address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
(etc.)

The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when using the “Email a Friend” form only to email the article. We do not retain the information you provide on the “Email a Friend” form or use it in any other way. Once the article is sent to your friend, their information is deleted from our system.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can sign up for our email newsletter and receive a weekly email message with health news updates. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you indicate that you wish to sign up for the newsletter.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

If you created an account when you placed an order, you can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into “My Account.” We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. If you did not create an account, you can change your information by contacting us at [support@peoplespharmacy.com](mailto:support@peoplespharmacy.com)

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (800) 732-2334 or send us an email at [support@peoplespharmacy.com](mailto:support@peoplespharmacy.com).

##### Tired of the ads on our website?

Now you can browse our website **completely ad-free** for just **$5 / month**. Stay up to date on breaking health news and support our work without the distraction of advertisements.

##### Join over 150,000 Subscribers at The People's Pharmacy

We're empowering you to make wise decisions about your own health, by providing you with essential health information about both medical and alternative treatment options.
